<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<!--icode==================================================== -->
		
		<string-array name="c_way">
        <item >C is such a powerful, dominant and supple language. C-way is an event which gives all c/c++ programmers a golden opportunity to showcase their coding skills .so test your c/c++ coding skills and have a pleasant experience to compete with other and be an Ultimate C Programmer!!!
         </item>
        <item> 
 			  Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
        <item >
Sonika Malani\n
Sanjana Chhabira                                                
</item>
<item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="javaguru">
        <item >If you are really excited to make your own app, to develope a software using an object-oriented language then this is the event where you can apply your java skills, compete with bests and be the Javaguru!!!          
        </item>
        <item>Coming Soon
    	</item>
        <item >Coming Soon     
        </item>
        <item >Anirudh Loya\n
			   Bhairavee Chitnis
            
        </item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="technohunt">
        <item>You must have definitely seen the Amazing race and liked it also. In Technovanza you will experience but in a different sort of way. It is a team event in which you have to locate the clues at different locations of the campus to unlock a hidden file and thus go to the next round. So get ready to enjoy the amazing coding race.
            </item>
        <item>Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Coming Soon     
        </item>
        <item >Aakash Adhikari\n
            Neha Kumari
            
        </item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
	<string-array name="ultimate_coder">
        <item >Ever wondered to experience most challenging coding competition if so, prepare yourself for an exciting journey of wonderful coding world.
Be an Ultimate Coder by showing your smartness and concentration!!!
         </item>
        <item> 
 			Coming Soon
 			</item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
            <item >Suraj Sunil Naik\n
                Akash Mane
</item>
<item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
		<string-array name="mission_sql">
        <item >If you love working with databases then this is the event for you. Get ready to solve the problems with difficulty level increasing with each problem.
         </item>
        <item>Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Yashodhan Gawde\n
Rohan Dandekar</item>
<item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="ai_wars">
        <item >Coming Soon
         </item>
        <item> Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Coming Soon </item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
<item >Coming Soon
    Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="codeswap">
        <item >Talent wins games, but teamwork wins championships. So, test your skills of Java and C along with your partner in Code Swap
event that involves lot of swapping and be Champions of coding world!!!
 </item>
        <item> Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Coming Soon</item>
        <item >Urmi Dabholkar\n
Tejasvi</item>
<item >Coming Soon</item>
    </string-array>
        
	
</resources>