<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="cancelled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">Unable to perform selected action because permissions were not granted.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="hello_user">Hello %1$s!</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="successfully_posted_post">Successfully posted \'%1$s\'.\nPost ID: %2$s</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="status_update">Updating status for %1$s at %2$s</string>
    <string name="photo_post">Photo Post</string>
    <string name="you_picked">You picked:</string>
    <string name="no_friends_selected">&lt;No friends selected&gt;</string>
    <string name="no_place_selected">&lt;No place selected&gt;</string>
    <string name="pick_seattle_place">Pick a Seattle Place</string>
    
    <string name="exception">Exception: %1$s</string>
     <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_websearch">Web search</string>
    <string name="app_not_available">Sorry, there\'s no web browser available</string>
    <string name="register"><u>Create an Account</u></string>
    
    <string name="app_name">Technovanza \'14</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="media">Gallery</string>
    <string name="news">Twitter</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="twitter_welcome">Welcome to Techno-Twitter\!</string>
    <string name="twitter_signin_notification">You need to sign into Twitter to authorize the app</string>
    <string name="twitter_signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="technovanza">\@Technovanza</string>
    <string name="tweet_btn_content_desc">Button for posting tweets</string>
    <string name="app_id">295439500634510</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="housecup">Housecup</string>
    <string name="green">Green Griffin</string>
    <string name="red">Red Phoenix</string>
    <string name="blue">Blue Dragon</string>
    <string name="house_info">"I\'ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I\'ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I\'ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I\'ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed."-Michael Jordan
\n 
\n
The introduction of the House Cup last year in Technovanza, motivated by the theme, \'Integrating TO Perfection\' was a grand success. It was a fierce battle between all the departments which led to a lot of nail biting moments towards the end due to the cut-throat competition. In the end, Blue Dragons emerged victorious.
\n\n
House Cup was introduced to act as a platform where both technical expertise and a passion for one\'s branch are of utmost importance. This is not only an attempt to encourage participation among students,  but also to build a healthy network among students, the competition requiring coordination amongst everyone belonging to different years of their education in the institute. House Cup will thus create an atmosphere of overall growth and development in the campus, taking us closer to the dream of taking technology to the society.  
\n\n
The House Cup integrates different branches into houses, leaving each house with sufficient knowledge about mechanics, electronics and coding. Also, interaction between different departments will turn the competition into a great learning experience, dissolving the boundaries between the departments. This in turn will help students to take multi-dimensional approaches to solve a problem.
\n\n
Is there anyne who hasn\'t dreamed of the sorting hat being placed upon his head and being selected into Gryffindor after watching Harry Potter! Now is your chance to live the dream. And like Michael Jordan said, don\'t be afraid to fail, for failure is the first step towards success.
</string>
</resources>

